SANKALP YADAV

Kolkata, West Bengal, India



sankalp ma@srmuniv.edu.in



linkedin.com/in/sankalp-yadav-388210191

Summary

Experienced Representative with a demonstrated history of working in the e-learning industry. Skilled in Mongodb, Express, React, Nodejs, Python (Programming Language), Mentoring, HTML, and JavaScript. Strong professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering from SRM University.

Experience

Frontend Developer

PharmaQuant

Jun 2022 - Present (8 months)

Software Developer

SalaryBox

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022 (3 months)

Attain Wentor

AttainU

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022 (6 months)

Representative

AttainU

Apr 2021 - Feb 2022 (11 months)

CR

Attain Trainee

AttainU

Apr 2021 - Feb 2022 (11 months)

Education



SRM University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering

2016 - 2020

Skills

React.js • Tailwind CSS • Python (Programming Language) • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Node.js • Bootstrap • MongoDB • Express.js